<resources>
    <string name="app_name">107AB0008_HW7_2</string>
    <string name="recipe_name">Recipe</string>
    <string name="total_recipe">
        Key Lime Pie:This Key Lime Pie is an American classic. Ours is made with lime juice and sweetened condensed milk in a graham cracker crust and topped with whipped cream. Use key limes if you have them, otherwise substitute regular limes.
        #Grasshopper Pie:Here\'s Grandma\'s favorite Grasshopper Pie. Her version is made with marshmallows in the filling (skip the gelatin!) and an Oreo cookie crust. A classic!
        #Chocolate Swiss Roll Cake:This chocolate sponge cake is filled with whipped cream and coated in a thin layer of ganache to create the perfect chocolate swiss roll. All of your childhood dreams definitely just came true.
    </string>

    <string name="recipe_1">
        Ingredients\nFor the Crust:\n1 1/2 cups finely ground graham crackers (from about 9 crackers, 145g)\n1/4 cup butter, melted\n3 tablespoons white granulated sugar\n\nFor the Filling:\n1 tablespoon lime zest for filling plus 1/2 teaspoon for the topping\n3 egg yolks\n1 (14-ounce) can sweetened condensed milk\n1/2 cup lime juice (from about 20 key limes or 4 to 6 regular limes) \n\nFor the Whipped cream:\n3/4 cup heavy whipping cream\n1 tablespoon powdered sugar\n1/8 teaspoon vanilla extract\n\n
        Method\n1. Make the graham cracker crust:\nPreheat oven to 350°F. Mix the ground graham crackers, melted butter, and sugar in a bowl.\n\nPour into a 9-inch pie dish and spread the graham cracker mixture with your fingers, all over the inside of the pie dish in an even layer. You can use your fingers to do this, and then use the bottom and sides of a measuring cup or drinking glass to make smooth.\n\n
        Bake at 350°F for 10 minutes, then remove and set aside.\n\n
        2. Make the lime filling:\nPut the egg yolks into a medium bowl. Using an electric mixer or whisking by hand, beat until the yolks thicken and lighten up a bit in color, about 3 minutes.\n\nBeat in the lime zest and sweetened condensed milk for another 2 minutes.\n\nWhisk in the lime juice until smooth.\n\n
        3. Bake:\nPour filling into the prepared graham cracker crust and bake at 350°F in the middle rack for only 10 minutes, until the filling is just set.\n\n
        4. Chill:\nRemove from oven and let cool to room temperature. Chill in the refrigerator for an hour to overnight.\n\n
        5. Make whipped cream topping:\nFor a good sturdy whipped cream topping, it helps to start with a chilled bowl and very cold heavy whipping cream.\n\nPour the cream into a large chilled bowl. Add the powdered sugar (sifted is best) and vanilla. Use an electric mixer (or whip by hand if your gym membership ran out and you want the exercise), start on low speed and increase the speed to the highest level. Whip for several minutes until firm enough to hold shape.\n\n
        Don\'t over-whip or you\'ll make butter.\n\nSpread the whipped cream over the top of the chilled key lime pie. Sprinkle with a little more lime zest. Chill until ready to serve.\n
    </string>

    <string name="recipe_2">
        Ingredients\n30 Oreo cookies (60 halves), fillings discarded, cookies crushed fine\n6 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted\n3/4 cup whole milk\n24 large marshmallows\n1/4 cup creme de menthe liqueur\n2 tablespoons white creme de cacao\n1 to 2 drops green food coloring, optional\n1 cup heavy cream\nChocolate shavings to top, optional\n
        Method\n
        1. Preheat the oven:\nPreheat oven to 425°F.\n
        2. Make the Oreo cookie crust:\nIn a bowl, mix crushed Oreo cookie halves and 6 tablespoons of the butter. A small handful of the crumbs should hold together when you squeeze it in your fist. If it crumbles apart, add additional water, 1 tablespoon at a time, until it holds together\n\nPat into bottom and up sides of 10 inch pie dish. Press firmly with the bottom of a cup to tamp down and compact the crust into the pie dish.\n\nBake in oven for 5 to 10 minutes; remove from oven and cool completely.\n\nOnce cooled, place in freezer to chill.\n\n
        3. Make the marshmallow mixture:\nIn saucepan over medium heat, warm the milk until steaming, but not boiling. Add the marshmallows and stir gently until the marshmallows have melted.\n\nRemove the pan from heat and cool to room temperature, then chill in the fridge until cool to the touch. If you want, you can speed up the cooling process by setting the pan in an ice water bath. (If the mixture is room temperature or warmer, it has a tendency to break when you add the remaining ingredients.)\n\n
        4. Mix the in the liquors and whip the heavy cream:\nAdd creme de menthe and creme de cacao to the cooled marshmallow mixture, and mix well. Add a drop or two of green food dye if desired.\n\nWith a hand mixer or a stand mixer, whip the the cream until it forms stiff peaks. Fold the whipped cream into the milk and marshmallow mixture in three separate additions. Continue folding and gently mixing until no more streaks of white remain.\n\n
        5. Pour the filling into the crust and freeze:\nPour the filling into the crust and freeze for at least 3 hours. (Cover loosely with foil after 3 hours if you\'re going to leave it in the freezer longer.)\n\nServe with a dollop of whipped cream and sprinkle with chocolate shavings, if desired.\n
    </string>

    <string name="recipe_3">
        Ingredients\nFor the chocolate sponge cake\n\n3/4 cup (100g) cake flour\n1/2 cup (56g) cocoa powder\n3 1/2 tablespoons (26g) cornstarch\n3/4 cups (170g) granulated sugar\n6 large eggs, room temperature\n1/2 teaspoon (3g) kosher salt\n4 tablespoons (58g) melted unsalted butter\n1 teaspoon vanilla extract\n2 tablespoons cocoa powder (for dusting the tea towel)\nFor the stabilized whipped cream\n\n1 1/2 tablespoons cold water\n1 teaspoon plain gelatin powder\n1 1/2 cups heavy cream\n1/2 cup (50g) powdered sugar\n1 teaspoon vanilla extract\nFor the chocolate ganache\n\n1 cup (170g) semi-sweet chocolate chips\n1/2 cup heavy cream\n1 teaspoon vanilla extract, optional\nSpecial equipment\n\nHalf sheet pan (18 x 13 x 2-inches)\nTea towel\nParchment paper\n\n
        Method\n
        1.Sift the dry ingredients:\nInto a large bowl, sift together the cake flour, cocoa powder, and cornstarch three times. Set the dry ingredients aside.\n\n
        2. Warm sugar in the oven while it preheats:\nLine the half-sheet pan with parchment paper, then sprinkle the sugar onto the paper in an even layer.\n\nPlace the pan in the oven. Set the oven to 400°F. You\’ll have the sugar in the oven while it preheats and remove it from the oven when it is warm to the touch, in step 4.\n\n
        3. Whisk the eggs in a stand mixer:\nWhile the sugar is warming, use a stand mixer fitted with the whisk attachment to lightly beat the eggs, at low speed, until they look foamy with small bubbles, for 30 to 45 seconds.\nHow to Convert Stand Mixer Instructions to a Hand Mixer (and Vice Versa)\nREAD MORE:\n\n
        4. Add the sugar to the eggs:\nBy now, the sugar should be warm to the touch. Remove the pan from the oven, hold the parchment paper by the sides and, while the mixer is still running, sprinkle the warm sugar into the eggs, followed by the salt.\n\nOnce all of the sugar has been added to the eggs, increase the mixer’s speed to medium-high. Whip the mixture, until lemon-yellow and very thick, about 8 minutes.\n
        5. Prepare the sheet pan:\nWhile the eggs are whipping, lightly spray the cooled half-sheet jelly roll pan with baking spray (be sure to not spray the sides). Line the bottom of the sheet pan with the sheet of parchment paper you used to hold the sugar (or a new one).\n\n
        6. Sift in the dry ingredients and add the butter and vanilla:\nOnce the eggs have finished whipping, remove the bowl from the stand mixer and sift the dry ingredients into the mixer bowl with the eggs.\n\nUse a large rubber spatula, to gently fold the flour into the eggs. To fold in the eggs use the rubber spatula to scrape around the sides of the bowl, in toward the center of the bowl to encapsulate the flour in the eggs. You want to lift the egg mixture over the flour. Continue doing this gently, to avoid deflating the eggs too much, until no streaks of flour remain.\n\nWhen most of the flour has been folded in, add the melted butter and the vanilla. The mixture will go from voluminous to deflated but will still look thick and glossy after you\’ve folded in the flour and butter.\n\n
        7. Pour batter into prepared sheet and bake:\nPour the batter into the prepared sheet pan. Use an offset spatula to evenly spread and level out the batter in the pan. Give the pan three or four gentle taps against the countertop to expel any large bubbles. Bake the cake for 10 to 12 minutes. The cake will have doubled in size and will feel spongy when you press gently on the center.\n\n
        8. Sift cocoa powder over a tea towel:\nLightly dust a clean tea towel by sifting the cocoa powder over it.\n\n
        9. Flip cake out onto tea towel:\nOnce the cake has finished baking, remove the pan from the oven. Use a knife to separate the cake from the sides of the pan and immediately flip the cake onto the cocoa-dusted towel. Holding the pan from a low position will minimize cocoa spraying everywhere when you flip the cake out.\n\n
        10. Roll the cake and cool on rack:\nQuickly, but carefully, it is still hot, starting with the long edge, roll the cake into a tube shape. You don\'t need to remove the parchment paper. Allow the cake to cool in this shape on a cooling rack for 45 minutes.\n\n
        11. Combine water and gelatin to make stabilized whipped cream:\nToward the end of the cooling time, prepare the stabilized whipped cream. In a 1-cup microwave-safe bowl, combine the cold water and powdered gelatin.\n\nHeat the mixture in the microwave for 15-20 seconds on high. Once the mixture bubbles, remove it from the microwave and allow it to cool, but not firm up. The mixture will be runny and the gelatin will have dissolved.\n\n
        12. Whip the heavy cream:\nPour the heavy cream into a mixing bowl. Use an electric hand mixer fitted with the whisk attachment. Set it to medium speed for 2 minutes or until the beater leaves behind ribbons in the cream.\n\n
        13. Add in the gelatin, powdered sugar, and vanilla:\nReduce the mixer\’s speed to low and drizzle the gelatin in slowly. Once all of the gelatin has been added, add in the powdered sugar and vanilla. Stop the mixer and scrape down the bowl.\n\n
        14. Finish the whipped cream:\nBegin mixing again, this time on medium-high for another 3 to 4 minutes, or until the whipped cream holds stiff peaks when the beaters are removed from it, the cream should stand straight up.\n\nIf the cake is not yet cool to the touch, store the cream in a covered container in the fridge until you\’re ready to fill the cake.\n\n
        15. Unroll the cake:\nOnce the cake has cooled and is no longer warm to the touch, carefully unroll it and remove the parchment paper.\n\n
        16. Spread whipped cream on cake and reroll the cake:\nSpread a 1/8 to 1/4-inch layer of the whipped cream onto the cake, leaving a 1-inch margin on one of the short ends. Beginning on the cream-covered short end, tightly roll the cake back into a tube. Use the towel to roll the tube tightly toward the other end.\n\n
        17. Wrap cake in plastic wrap and refrigerate:\nWrap the tube snugly in plastic film. Twist the ends of the wrapping to create a tight cylindrical shape. Refrigerate the chocolate swiss roll for at least 2 hours to allow it to set.\n\n
        18. Prepare the chocolate ganache:\nAn hour before you plan to serve the Swiss roll, prepare the chocolate ganache. To make the ganache add the heavy cream to a 1-quart microwave-safe bowl. Place in the microwave for 1 minute 30 seconds, or until it begins to steam. You can also do this in a pot on the stove. You just want it to warm through, not boil.\n\nAdd the chocolate chips and vanilla to the bowl and shimmy the bowl slightly so that all of the chips are covered by the cream. Allow the chocolate to sit in the cream for 3 to 4 minutes.\n\nWhisk the cream and chocolate together until smooth. If chunks remain, heat the ganache in the microwave for 20 seconds, before whisking again. Allow the ganache to cool at room temperature for 12 to 15 minutes and firm up slightly.\n\n
        19. Unwrap and glaze the chocolate swiss roll:\nRemove the swiss roll from the fridge and remove the plastic covering. Place the roll on a cooling rack set over a sheet pan.\n\nPour the ganache over the top of the roll and use an offset spatula or the back of a spoon to cover the roll evenly in the chocolate. If you want to double the ganache, to use up all of the ganache, scoop up the excess from the pan underneath and repeat the pouring steps.\n\nTransfer the cake to a platter and refrigerate it until the ganache feels slightly tacky to the touch, or 20 minutes.\n\n
        20. Serve:\nSlice and serve. Store leftovers covered in the fridge and enjoy within 2 days.
    </string>
    <string name="clickedItemIndex">0</string>
</resources>